Prescott S. Bush Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Press Releases, undated, 1952-1962
  - Protection of Stamford and Mystic against Hurricane Flood—Engineers report, 1959 February 6 (Box 8:, Folder 559)
  - Civil Rights—Discrimination in labor unions, 1959 February 9 (Box 8:, Folder 560)
  - Migration of CT Industry, 1959 February 13 (Box 8:, Folder 561)
  - Migration of CT Industry, 1959 February 14 (Box 8:, Folder 562)
  - Plan for protecting Pawcatuck, 1959 February 16 (Box 8:, Folder 563)
  - Grant for Education—Middletown, 1959 February 17 (Box 8:, Folder 564)
  - Education bills, 1959 February 19 (Box 8:, Folder 565)
  - State Assistance on urban development, 1959 February 19 (Box 8:, Folder 566)
  - Analysis of depressed area bills, 1959 February 22 (Box 8:, Folder 567)
  - Torrington and Winsted dams—appropriations bills, 1959 February 22 (Box 8:, Folder 568)
  - Area assistance bills before Congress, 1959 February 27 (Box 8:, Folder 569)
  - Area assistance bills before Congress, 1959 March (Box 8:, Folder 570)
  - “Capital Cloakroom”, 1959 March 5 (Box 8:, Folder 571)
  - Employment discrimination to Commission on Civil Rights, 1959 March 5 (Box 8:, Folder 572)
  - Torrington and Winsted dams—preconstruction planning funds, 1959 March 11 (Box 8:, Folder 573)
  - Protection of Stamford—Hurricane project, 1959 March 13 (Box 8:, Folder 574)
  - Protection of Pawcatuck—Flood protection, 1959 March 13 (Box 8:, Folder 575)
  - Dams at Naugatuck River—Northfield Branch, Hancock, and Hop Brook, 1959 March 13 (Box 8:, Folder 576)
  - Kennedy/Ervin bill, 1959 March 16 (Box 8:, Folder 577)
  - Labor legislation, 1959 March 13 (Box 8:, Folder 578)
  - Depressed areas bill, 1959 March 19 (Box 8:, Folder 579)
  - Colchester Post Office, 1959 March 21 (Box 8:, Folder 580)
  - Submarine contract awards other than Electric Boat, 1959 March 24 (Box 8:, Folder 581)
  - Preliminary details for 1960 Census, 1959 March 27 (Box 8:, Folder 582)
  - Inflation, 1959 March 27 (Box 8:, Folder 583)
  - Review; Easter; Democrats; Spenders, 1959 March 30 (Box 8:, Folder 584)
  - Invitations to Bid to Electric Boat, 1959 April 7 (Box 8:, Folder 585)
  - Thurston Morton for Chairman, Republican National Committee, 1959 April 7 (Box 8:, Folder 586)
  - Alcorn, Morton, Mutual security Act, 1959 April 10 (Box 8:, Folder 587)
  - Polaris Program, 1959 April 13 (Box 8:, Folder 588)
  - Fairer taxation of non-residents by NY, MA, 1959 April 15 (Box 8:, Folder 589)
  - Cannon—Flood control project, 1959 April 20 (Box 8:, Folder 590)
  - Tariff Commission—Mandatory quota on imports of stainless steel, 1959 April 21 (Box 8:, Folder 591)
  - Imports of stainless steel, 1959 April 24 (Box 9:, Folder 592)
  - Stainless steel flatware, Interstate Highway toll reimbursement, taxes on non-residents, 1959 April 24 (Box 9:, Folder 593)
  - “Faith of Our Fathers”, 1959 April 26 (Box 9:, Folder 594)
  - Toll road reimbursement, 1959 April 27 (Box 9:, Folder 595)
  - May Day; Law Day [Georgetown]; International Court of Justice, 1959 May 1 (Box 9:, Folder 596)
  - Speech—“Foreign Economic Policy and Inflation” Manchester, NH, 1959 May 3 (Box 9:, Folder 597)
  - Polish Constitution Day, 1959 May 5 (Box 9:, Folder 598)
  - Foreign Industrial Competition, Inflation, 1959 May 8 (Box 9:, Folder 599)
  - Economy, 1959 May 11 (Box 9:, Folder 600)
  - Toll Road reimbursement, S. 1714, S. 570, 1959 May 19 (Box 9:, Folder 601)
  - Trading with the Enemy Act S. 2012, 1959 May 20 (Box 9:, Folder 602)
  - Highway; Toll reimbursement; Employment; Housing Legislation, 1959 May 22 (Box 9:, Folder 603)
  - “Equal Time”-FCC, 1959 May 22 (Box 9:, Folder 604)
  - Health; Welfare, 1959 May 25 (Box 9:, Folder 605)
  - S. 2060, Uniform Cost-sharing on Flood Control projects, 1959 May 28 (Box 9:, Folder 606)
  - Agriculture—Strauss, other nominations, 1959 June 5 (Box 9:, Folder 607)
  - Strauss nomination, 1959 June 6 (Box 9:, Folder 608)
  - Fred Seaton—Oyster eradication, 1959 June 11 (Box 9:, Folder 609)
  - Opposition conference report on Housing bill, 1959 June 19 (Box 9:, Folder 610)
  - Economy; airport bill vote; highway reimbursement, 1959 June 19 (Box 9:, Folder 611)
  - Multi-State taxation bill, S. 2213, 1959 June 22 (Box 9:, Folder 612)
  - Economy, 1959 June 22 (Box 9:, Folder 613)
  - Manufacturing problems and effects of shopping centers Uconn research grant, 1959 June 23 (Box 9:, Folder 614)
  - Inflation of sound dollar for economic growth, 1959 June 29 (Box 9:, Folder 615)
  - Price Stability for Economic Growth—Interim report, 1959 June 29 (Box 9:, Folder 616)
  - Polaris Sub contract to Electric Boat, 1959 July 1 (Box 9:, Folder 617)
  - $1.6 million to University of Bridgeport for dormitory, 1959 July 1 (Box 9:, Folder 618)
  - Urban renewal—Seymour, CT, 1959 July 1 (Box 9:, Folder 619)
  - Urban renewal—East Granby, Granbrook Park, 1959 July 2 (Box 9:, Folder 620)
  - Defense, Reader's Digest, Inflation, 1959 July 13 (Box 9:, Folder 621)
  - Starfish Amendment, 1959 July 6 (Box 9:, Folder 622)
  - Foreign Policy, 1959 July 6 (Box 9:, Folder 623)
  - Construction of local Flood protection on W. Branch on Naugatuck, 1959 July 6 (Box 9:, Folder 624)
  - Urban renewal—Farmington, 1959 July 6 (Box 9:, Folder 625)
  - Urban renewal—Ansonia, Broad Street, 1959 July 7 (Box 9:, Folder 626)
  - Urban renewal project—Norwalk wall, 1959 July 8 (Box 9:, Folder 627)
  - Housing bill, S. 2378, 1959 July 14 (Box 9:, Folder 628)
  - Housing bill, S. 2378, Failures of 86th Congress, 1959 July 17 (Box 9:, Folder 629)
  - Failures of 86th Congress—labor, housing, civil rights, inflation, 1959 July 20 (Box 9:, Folder 630)
  - Amendment to S. 2378 (Housing), cost sharing by states, 1959 July 21 (Box 9:, Folder 631)
  - S. 2213 Senate Finance Committee, 1959 July 21 (Box 9:, Folder 632)
  - Housing hearing on veto and S. 2378, 1959 July 27 (Box 9:, Folder 633)
  - Broadcast facilities exchange—USSR and USA, 1959 July 30 (Box 9:, Folder 634)
  - Relief of Sporting arms manufacturers, 1959 July 31 (Box 9:, Folder 635)
  - Labor, Nixon's tour of Russia, multi-state taxes, housing, 1959 July 31 (Box 9:, Folder 636)
  - State Highway department action on highway contracts, 1959 August 5 (Box 9:, Folder 637)
  - Exchange of radio and TV facilities USSR, 1959 August 10 (Box 9:, Folder 638)
  - H.R. 8575 Military construction appropriations, 1959 August 10 (Box 9:, Folder 639)
  - McElroy's Invitation to Krushchev, 1959 August 11 (Box 9:, Folder 640)
  - Veto of Housing bill—override attempt, 1959 August 12 (Box 9:, Folder 641)
  - Griffen-Landrum bill, 1959 August 14 (Box 9:, Folder 642)
  - Labor, housing, highway, 1959 August 14 (Box 9:, Folder 643)
  - Dedication of Bush-McCormack dam—Torrington, 1959 August 20 (Box 9:, Folder 644)
  - Congress should remain in session until business completed, 1959 August 28 (Box 9:, Folder 645)
  - Labor union/Management reform bill, 1959 September 3 (Box 9:, Folder 646)
  - Second Public Works appropriations bill—veto, 1959 September 10 (Box 9:, Folder 647)
  - Urban renewal projects pending approval, 1959 September 11 (Box 9:, Folder 648)
  - Third Housing bill; Presidential vetos; Civil Rights, 1959 September 11 (Box 9:, Folder 649)
  - Review of 86th Congress, 1st session—lack of fiscal responsibility by Democrats; gains in labor reform, 1959 September 14 (Box 9:, Folder 650)
  - Speech—Connecticut Association for Retarded Children, 1959 September 26 (Box 9:, Folder 651)
  - Civil Defense shelter at Hartford Public High School, 1959 September 29 (Box 9:, Folder 652)
  - Speech—Fiscal responsibility, Lakeville/Litchfield County Women's Organization, 1959 September 29 (Box 9:, Folder 653)
  - Speech—Council of Polish Organizations, Pulaski Day Ceremonies, 1959 October 5 (Box 9:, Folder 654)
  - Hartford Republican luncheon—Democrats and 1960 Outlook, 1959 October 6 (Box 9:, Folder 655)
  - Waterbury—Tariff and Trade; AFL resolution on trade; Import quotas, 1959 October 7 (Box 9:, Folder 656)
  - Kaman Aircraft Award, 1959 October 8 (Box 9:, Folder 657)
  - Speech—Fiscal Responsibility, White Sulphur Springs, WV Savings Bank Association, 1959 October 9 (Box 9:, Folder 658)
  - World's Fair, 1959 October 22 (Box 9:, Folder 659)
  - Speech—Fiscal responsibility before LIAA, 1959 December 9 (Box 9:, Folder 660)
  - Statement of Opening of 2nd Session, 1960 January 6 (Box 9:, Folder 661)
  - State of the Union message, 1960 January 7 (Box 9:, Folder 662)
  - Resolution to prevent Communist Movement in Western Hemisphere—Caribbean, 1960 January 7 (Box 9:, Folder 663)
  - Candidates to Compete for Academies, 1960 January 12 (Box 9:, Folder 664)
  - S.J. Res. 148 resolution for Dr. Dooley, 1960 January 13 (Box 9:, Folder 665)
  - Caribbean resolution, judgeship appointments, State of the Union message, 1960 January 15 (Box 9:, Folder 666)
  - President's Budget message, 1960 January 18 (Box 9:, Folder 667)
  - Northeastern water and related land resources, 1960 January 18 (Box 9:, Folder 668)
  - JEC Minority members' report on Employment, Growth and Price levels, 1960 January 26 (Box 9:, Folder 669)
  - Criticism of Administration “Salute to Ike” dinner, 1960 January 28 (Box 9:, Folder 670)
  - Defense Secretary Thomas Gates, 1960 January 29 (Box 9:, Folder 671-672)
  - Javits resolution against religious desecration, 1960 February 1 (Box 10:, Folder 673)
  - Military Construction bill- CT projects, 1960 February 4 (Box 10:, Folder 674)
  - Flood control reservoirs for Naugatuck River Valley to provide protection for fish and wildlife, 1960 February 11 (Box 10:, Folder 675)
  - Urban renewal, 1960 February 11 (Box 10:, Folder 676)
  - Speech—“Peanuts and Missiles” Lincoln Day, 1960 February 12 (Box 10:, Folder 677)
  - Farm program—Middletown, 1960 February 13 (Box 10:, Folder 678)
  - Urban renewal, 1960 February 14 (Box 10:, Folder 679)
  - Handling of military secrets, 1960 February 14 (Box 10:, Folder 680)
  - Urban renewal, problems arising from relocation—Hartford Rotary Club, 1960 February 15 (Box 10:, Folder 681)
  - Bozrah—Polaris missiles as Nation's major strategic weapon, 1960 February 16 (Box 10:, Folder 682)
  - Democrats control of Congress hurting small businessmen and American Families, 1960 February 17 (Box 10:, Folder 683)
  - Air Force Training manual, 1960 February 17 (Box 10:, Folder 684)
  - Waterbury Post Office facility, 1960 February 18 (Box 10:, Folder 685)
  - Civil Rights, 1960 February 19 (Box 10:, Folder 686)
  - University of Hartford, 1960 February 19 (Box 10:, Folder 687)
  - Correspondence—defense, farms and education, 1960 February 26 (Box 10:, Folder 688)
  - Correspondence—defense, 1960 February 29 (Box 10:, Folder 689)
  - Exploitation of “Round-the-Clock” sessions, Civil Rights, 1960 March 2 (Box 10:, Folder 690)
  - General Itschner, 1960 March 11 (Box 10:, Folder 691-692)
  - Dr. York, 1960 March 25 (Box 10:, Folder 693-694)
  - Anthony F. Arpaia -NHRR, 1960 April 5 (Box 10:, Folder 695-696)
  - Civil Rights Act of 1960, 1960 April 8 (Box 10:, Folder 697)
  - New London County and Eastern CT Labor, 1960 April 12 (Box 10:, Folder 698)
  - $750,000 for Bridgeport Harbor, 1960 April 13 (Box 10:, Folder 699)
  - Judges J. Joseph Smith and William H. Timbers, 1960 April 19 (Box 10:, Folder 700)
  - Ansonia Federal Flood Control project, 1960 April 20 (Box 10:, Folder 701)
  - Civil Rights, 1960 April 20 (Box 10:, Folder 702)
  - Shellfishing Center at Milford, CT, 1960 April 20 (Box 10:, Folder 703)
  - Civil Rights, 1960 April 21 (Box 10:, Folder 704-705)
  - Senate Subcommittee on Flood control—rivers and harbors on H.R. 7634, 1960 April 25 (Box 10:, Folder 706)
  - Housing, 1960 May 2 (Box 10:, Folder 707)
  - Summit Conference and International Relations, 1960 May 3 (Box 10:, Folder 708)
  - Honesty v. Political comments—NY Chamber of Commerce, 1960 May 5 (Box 10:, Folder 709)
  - Mutual Security and Foreign Aid, 1960 May 6 (Box 10:, Folder 710-711)
  - “Senator Bush would equalize flood costs”, 1960 May 7 (Box 10:, Folder 712)
  - American plane shot down over Soviet Union, 1960 May 9 (Box 10:, Folder 713)
  - Textile and woolen industry meeting, 1960 May 11 (Box 10:, Folder 714)
  - President's veto of S. 722, Area redevelopment bill, 1960 May 16 (Box 10:, Folder 715)
  - Captain Edward L. Beach, “Triton”, 1960 May 16 (Box 10:, Folder 716-717)
  - “The Party of Responsibility”, VT Republican State Convention, 1960 May 21 (Box 10:, Folder 718)
  - Captain Edward L. Beach, “Triton”, 1960 May 22 (Box 10:, Folder 719)
  - Elks National Youth Leadership contest winners, 1960 May 24 (Box 10:, Folder 720)
  - Health Insurance for Elderly, 1960 June 1 (Box 10:, Folder 721)
  - Forand Bill, Medicare program, Medical Care and Hospitalization for the Aged, 1960 June 3 (Box 10:, Folder 722-723)
  - Address—CT Republican State Convention, 1960 June 6 (Box 10:, Folder 724)
  - Tariff Negotiations, 1960 June 14 (Box 10:, Folder 725)
  - Adjournment, Nixon and Rockefeller, Electric Boat contracts, CT Committee problem, unfinished legislation, 1960 June 17 (Box 10:, Folder 726)
  - Abner Sibal, 1960 June 19 (Box 10:, Folder 727)
  - Summit Conference and legislative issues, 1960 June 20 (Box 10:, Folder 728)
  - “Carey Cronan” radio program, WHAY, 1960 June 23 (Box 10:, Folder 729)
  - Hartford Urban renewal project, Windsor Street, 1960 July 20 (Box 10:, Folder 730)
  - President's message—Communism and domestic problems, 1960 August 8 (Box 10:, Folder 731)
  - Edwin Smith—Town Chairman, Colebrook, 1960 August 13 (Box 10:, Folder 732)
  - Minimum wage, 1960 August 15 (Box 10:, Folder 733)
  - “The Candidates and the Issues of the 1960 Campaign”, 1960 September 15 (Box 10:, Folder 734)
  - Correspondence—ABC to FCC, 1960 September 25 (Box 10:, Folder 735)
  - Senator Jackson's accusation of Nixon, 1960 October 4 (Box 10:, Folder 736)
  - Campaign in Miami, FL, 1960 October 11 (Box 10:, Folder 737)
  - Trade Relations Council of the US annual meeting, 1960 October 26 (Box 10:, Folder 738)
  - “Urban Renewal—the Road Ahead”, Conference on Economic Development and Urban renewal in CT, CT Urban Renewal Assn., Yale Law School, 1960 December 6 (Box 10:, Folder 739)
  - Flood Protection project—Ansonia, Derby, Naugatuck River, Thomaston dam, 1960 December 22 (Box 10:, Folder 740)
  - Run for Re-election, 1960 December 30 (Box 10:, Folder 741)
  - Price stability amendment, Resolution on Item veto powers, 1961 January 5 (Box 10:, Folder 742)
  - Postmaster appointments, 1961 January 8 (Box 10:, Folder 743)
  - Cloture, Rule XXII, Filibuster, Civil Rights, 1961 January 9 (Box 10:, Folder 744)
  - Resolution to “Modernize the Monroe Doctrine”, 1961 January 9 (Box 10:, Folder 745)
  - “Modernize the Monroe Doctrine”, 1961 January 9 (Box 10:, Folder 746)
  - Flood protection for Ansonia, 1961 January 10 (Box 10:, Folder 747)
  - Mass transportation bill, 1961 January 11 (Box 10:, Folder 748)
  - Northeastern Water and Related land Resource Compact, 1961 January 12 (Box 10:, Folder 749)
  - Reimburse State for Free and toll highways, 1961 January 17 (Box 10:, Folder 750)
  - Civil Rights bills—7 provisions, 1961 January 18 (Box 10:, Folder 751)
  - Searle Pinney appointment, 1961 January 18 (Box 10:, Folder 752)
  - Bush's candidacy for re-election, 1961 January 23 (Box 10:, Folder 753)
  - Academy appointments, 1961 January 23 (Box 10:, Folder 754)
  - Imposition of Use Tax assessments, 1961 January 23 (Box 10:, Folder 755)
  - National Advisory Commission on Interstate Crime, 1961 January 25 (Box 10:, Folder 756)
  - Shellfisheries Research Center at Milford, CT, 1961 January 26 (Box 10:, Folder 757)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Affairs—proposed, 1961 January 26 (Box 10:, Folder 758)
  - Urban renewal and redevelopment projects, 1961 January 26 (Box 10:, Folder 759)
  - Speech—Urban renewal, 1961 January 26 (Box 10:, Folder 760)
  - Organized Crime bill, 1961 January 27 (Box 10:, Folder 762)
  - Naming of Thomaston dam, 1961 January 30 (Box 10:, Folder 763)
  - State of the Union message—Kennedy, 1961 January 30 (Box 10:, Folder 764)
  - National Science Foundation Grants to UConn and Yale, 1961 January 31 (Box 10:, Folder 765)
  - Correspondence—depressed areas bill, 1961 February 2 (Box 11:, Folder 766)
  - Depressed areas, Urban renewal, unemployment, 1961 February 3 (Box 11:, Folder 767)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1961 February 3 (Box 11:, Folder 768)
  - Increase opportunities—>Electric Boat, 1961 February 3 (Box 11:, Folder 769)
  - Unemployment compensation program, 1961 February 5 (Box 11:, Folder 770)
  - Employment and area development, 1961 February 5 (Box 11:, Folder 771)
  - Flood control and navigation projects in CT funds, 1961 February 9 (Box 11:, Folder 772)
  - Lincoln Day engagements, 1961 February 9 (Box 11:, Folder 773)
  - Speech—Naugatuck River Valley, Flood control, Urban renewal, distressed areas bill, 1961 February 12 (Box 11:, Folder 774)
  - Speech—Interstate Highway system, 1961 February 13 (Box 11:, Folder 775)
  - Distressed area bill and amendment, Urban renewal, 1961 February 14 (Box 11:, Folder 776)
  - CT Petroleum annual meeting, 1961 February 14 (Box 11:, Folder 777)
  - Hartford Council; Restrictions on Imports of Fuel Oils, 1961 February 14 (Box 11:, Folder 778)
  - Vice Admiral H. G. Rickover—Nuclear Power ship propulsion and American Educational Practices, 1961 February 15 (Box 11:, Folder 779)
  - Rickover—Education, Teachers, Schools and Federal Assistance, 1961 February 16 (Box 11:, Folder 780)
  - Nuclear power and ship propulsion; National defense; Polaris Ballistic missile submarine; Importance of pushing education in Senate; Education in Senate; Education in US and abroad, 1961 February 19 (Box 11:, Folder 781)
  - Rickover—Nuclear power ship propulsion, Polaris missile, Schools and education, 1961 February 19 (Box 11:, Folder 782)
  - Correspondence—Urban renewal, 1961 February 22 (Box 11:, Folder 783)
  - Hurricane Tidal flooding (Mystic) authorization, 1961 February 22 (Box 11:, Folder 784)
  - Flood protection projects and amendment, 1961 February 23 (Box 11:, Folder 785)
  - Urging bill approval, 1961 February 26 (Box 11:, Folder 786)
  - Northeastern Water and Related Land Resources Compact Congressional consent, 1961 March 1 (Box 11:, Folder 787)
  - Flood control program for CT, 1961 March 1 (Box 11:, Folder 788)
  - Bush newsletter—Jobs, depressed areas, urban renewal, health and welfare aid, education, flood control, Bush-McCormack Act, Honorary Scout, Peace Corps, Welcome to Washington, 1961 March 1 (Box 11:, Folder 789)
  - Bush-McCormack Act, Flood Control, Corps of Engineers, 1961 March 3 (Box 11:, Folder 790)
  - New Haven Railroad problems, 1961 March 3 (Box 11:, Folder 791)
  - Omnibus Judgeship bill, 1961 March 3 (Box 11:, Folder 792)
  - S. 1 Prohibition of Financial Assistance for business relocation (Depressed areas bill), 1961 March 3 (Box 11:, Folder 793)
  - Bush-McCormack Act of 1956, 1961 March 6 (Box 11:, Folder 794)
  - Editorial on Bush-McCormack Act, 1961 March 7 (Box 11:, Folder 795)
  - S. 1227 Granting National Defense Scholarships, 1961 March 7 (Box 11:, Folder 796)
  - Bush's Three Education bills, 1961 March 7 (Box 11:, Folder 797)
  - S. 1 Depressed areas bill, 1961 March 7 (Box 11:, Folder 798)
  - CT engagements, 1961 March 9 (Box 11:, Folder 799)
  - Anti-Pirating amendment, 1961 March 9 (Box 11:, Folder 800)
  - CT Junior Chamber of Commerce—Norwich, 1961 March 12 (Box 11:, Folder 801)
  - Education; President's program; area redevelopment program; minimum wage; housing bills; highway program, 1961 March 17 (Box 11:, Folder 802)
  - Foreign policy and defense; anti-pirating amendment; minimum wage, 1961 March 20 (Box 11:, Folder 803)
  - Endorsement of statement of US position in Laotian Crisis, 1961 March 24 (Box 11:, Folder 804)
  - Fiscal record; Polaris weapons; CANAL project; Bush appointment to Senate Committee on Problems of Aging, 1961 March 31 (Box 11:, Folder 805)
  - Bush newsletter, 1961 April 1 (Box 11:, Folder 806)
  - Bill Garrett, 1961 April 3 (Box 11:, Folder 807)
  - CANAL installation at Middletown, CT, 1961 April 4 (Box 11:, Folder 808)
  - Minimum wage, 1961 April 14 (Box 11:, Folder 809)
  - Don Larabee, 1961 April 17 (Box 11:, Folder 810-811)
  - CT Schedule, 1961 April 21 (Box 11:, Folder 812)
  - Murphy testimonial—Bristol urban renewal, 1961 April 23 (Box 11:, Folder 813)
  - Three weekend events in CT, 1961 April 25 (Box 11:, Folder 814)
  - Charles S. Rhyne, 1961 April 26 (Box 11:, Folder 815)
  - Radio broadcast, 1961 April 28 (Box 11:, Folder 816)
  - Charles S. Rhyne—Law Day, 1961 May 1 (Box 11:, Folder 817)
  - Bush Newsletter, 1961 May 1 (Box 11:, Folder 818)
  - National Association of Mutual Savings Banks Annual Conference, 1961 May 2 (Box 11:, Folder 819)
  - MORE program for Republican National Committee, 1961 May 3 (Box 11:, Folder 820)
  - “The 107th Anniversary of the Polish Constitution”, 1961 May 3 (Box 11:, Folder 821)
  - S. J. Res. 85—District of Columbia, 1961 May 11 (Box 11:, Folder 822)
  - Work stoppages at US missile sites, 1961 May 12 (Box 11:, Folder 823)
  - Senator McClellan, 1961 May 14 - 15 (Box 11:, Folder 824)
  - Speech—S. 1021, 1961 May 18 (Box 11:, Folder 825)
  - “School Assistance Act of 1961”, 1961 May 18 (Box 11:, Folder 826)
  - “Modified Bush Amendment”—anti-segregation amendment, 1961 May 22 (Box 11:, Folder 827)
  - Dr. Thomas Anthony Dooley, III, 1961 May 22 (Box 11:, Folder 828)
  - Memorial Day Weekend schedule, 1961 May 25 (Box 11:, Folder 829)
  - Inflation, 1961 May 25 (Box 11:, Folder 830)
  - Federal aid to Education, 1961 May 26 (Box 11:, Folder 831)
  - New England Senators' Conference, 1961 June 5 (Box 11:, Folder 832)
  - Man on the moon by 1970, 1961 June 6, 9 (Box 11:, Folder 833-834)
  - Dr. Alan T. Waterman, 1961 June 11 (Box 11:, Folder 835)
  - CT weekend schedule, 1961 June 13 (Box 11:, Folder 836)
  - Wheeler High School Graduation—North Stonington, CT, 1961 June 20 (Box 11:, Folder 837)
  - “Tax reduction hints and spending programs”, 1961 June 21 (Box 11:, Folder 838)
  - Cold War, Berlin Ultimatum, Mansfield's Berlin Proposal, Nuclear testing, 1961 June 23 (Box 11:, Folder 839)
  - Carey Cronan, 1961 June 23 (Box 11:, Folder 840)
  - Speech—Wheeler High School Graduation, 1961 June 23 (Box 11:, Folder 841)
  - Housing Act of 1961, 1961 June 27 (Box 11:, Folder 842)
  - Housing Act of 1961—Conference report, 1961 June 28 (Box 11:, Folder 843)
  - Kennedy Housing program, 1961 June 29 (Box 11:, Folder 844)
  - CT schedule of dates, 1961 July 1 - 5 (Box 11:, Folder 845-846)
  - Bush Newsletter, 1961 July 1 (Box 11:, Folder 847)
  - Crisis of New Haven Railroad, 1961 July 5 (Box 11:, Folder 848)
  - New Haven Railroad; President's program; Abolishing political appointments to Postmasters, 1961 July 6 (Box 11:, Folder 849)
  - Don Larrabee, 1961 July 6 (Box 11:, Folder 850)
  - White House rejection of New Haven Railroad, 1961 July 7 (Box 11:, Folder 851-852)
  - S. 2211 Tax relief to New Haven Railroad, 1961 July 10 (Box 11:, Folder 853-854)
  - Longevity step increases by Senate—mailing to Postal Workers, 1961 July 17 (Box 12:, Folder 855)
  - “Freedom of Nations”, 1961 July 18 (Box 12:, Folder 856)
  - Berlin Crisis, 1961 July 21 (Box 12:, Folder 857-858)
  - Berlin Crisis, 1961 July 26 (Box 12:, Folder 859)
  - Increased defense spending, 1961 July 27 (Box 12:, Folder 860)
  - New Haven Railroad and appointed trustees, 1961 July 27 (Box 12:, Folder 861)
  - “National needs and budget deficits”, 1961 July 27 (Box 12:, Folder 862)
  - HEW appropriations bill amendment, 1961 July 29 (Box 12:, Folder 863-864)
  - Fiscal prudence in government, amendments to limit spending in non-defense appropriations, 1961 July 29 (Box 12:, Folder 865)
  - Elimination of additional appropriations in HR 70351 Labor—HEW 1962, 1961 August 1 (Box 12:, Folder 866)